https://optirisk-systems.com/privacy-policy/

OptiRisk Systems Privacy PolicyHome>Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Optirisk
2019-02-05T12:02:38+00:00 OptiRisk Systems limited specializes in optimization and risk analytics and is renowned for its research and development of models and software systems in these domains. In the domain of Sentiment Analysis, OptiRisk has partnership with major news service providers. The company has researched and published the Handbook of News Analytics in Finance and Handbook of Sentiment Analysis in Finance. Our privacy policy sets out the use of information we gather. All personal data we collect is and will only be used as per The General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) that implemented on 25 May 2018.What information we collect:Our objective is to collect minimum required information in order to provide you access to our products and services. This may include an individual’s name, job title/position, contact information, affiliation and email address.How we collect information:Account RegistrationConferences and WorkshopsClient MeetingMarketing ActivitiesHow we protect information:Our employees protect all personal information and comply with non-disclosure agreement of the company. Data in our website is secured by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. Customer information in electronic form is stored in secure server and password protected databases. Our in-house networks use firewall.Disclosure:We do not disclose personal data to anyone unless it is absolutely required by law and guidelines.Cookies:Cookies are small files in client computers to collect some information about the user’s behavior in a website. We use cookies to analyze our page visit statistics.Marketing and Third Parties:We send newsletters, information about our events, conferences and products via third party email marketing service.Change in privacy policyOur privacy police may change subject to compliance with data protection law and change in our services.
